RIGHT NOW,
YOU PROBABLY TELL
I'M FIVE MINUTES AWAY.
SORRY, MY PHONE DIED.
NO, YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT.
IN FACT,
YOU MIGHT EVEN BE
LYING TO YOURSELF RIGHT
NOW
ABOUT WHY YOU OPENED
YOUTUBE.
WHERE LYING IS PHYSICALLY
IMPOSSIBLE,
WHERE EVERY SOUND THAT
COMES OUT OF YOUR
MOUTH
THAT WAS THE ONLY
WORLD THAT EXISTED.
IF A MONKEY SHRIEKED,
THERE WAS A LEOPARD.
IF A BIRD CALLED,
THERE WAS A HAWK.
IT WAS HARDWIRED SURVIVAL.
SOMEWHERE ON THE EAST
AFRICAN SAVANNAH,
AN ANCIENT HUMAN NAMED
GROG
DID SOMETHING THAT PERMANENTLY
BROKE REALITY.
WHILE FORAGING ALONE BEHIND
A ROCKY RIDGE,
GROG FOUND A WILD
BEEHIVE,
WHATEVER YOU FIND,
YOU BRING BACK AND
SHARE EQUALLY.
GROG LOOKED AT THE
HONEY.
THEN HE LOOKED BACK
TOWARD THE CAVE,
IF HE SHARED IT
WITH 30 HUNGRY TRIBE
MEMBERS, HE GOT ONE
STICKY MOUTHFUL.
IF HE KEPT IT
SECRET, HE FEASTED LIKE
A KING FOR WEEKS.
THERE WAS ONLY ONE
PROBLEM. HOW COULD HE
RETURN TO THE CAVE
WITH COMPLETELY EMPTY HANDS?
GROG DECIDED TO DESCRIBE
SOMETHING THAT DIDN'T EXIST.
WHEN HE WALKED INTO
THE FIRELIT CAVE AT
SUNSET,
THE TRIBE LEADER DEMANDED
TO KNOW WHERE HE
HAD BEEN.
GROG DIDN'T PANIC.
HE LOOKED THE LEADER
DEAD IN THE EYE,
CLUTCHED HIS CHEST IN
FAKE TERROR,
A PACK OF FEROCIOUS
HYENAS CHASED ME
THE TRIBE GASKED IN
HORROR.
THE LEADER PADDED GROG'S
SHOULDER, RELIEVED HE SURVIVED.
NOBODY QUESTIONED IT,
AND IN THAT SINGLE
SECOND, HUMAN HISTORY SHIFTED
FOREVER.
WITHOUT THROWING A SINGLE
PUNCH, GROG CONTROLLED THE
ENTIRE TRIBE.
AN UNSTOPPABLE BIOLOGICAL ARMS
RACE.
TO SURVIVE,
HUMAN BRAINS HAD TO
EVOLVE RAPIDLY.
NOT TO OUTSMART LIONS,
BUT TO OUTSMART EACH
OTHER.
OUR FRONTAL LOBES BALLOONED
IN SIZE
WHICH MEANS THE VERY
REASON YOU ARE SMART
ENOUGH TO UNDERSTAND THIS
VIDEO
IS BECAUSE YOUR ANCESTORS
WERE PROFESSIONAL LIARS.